[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 4, "question": "Has there been a moment when you could have veered down the Charlie Sheen route?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 5, "answer": "Sure, there's always a moment for anybody.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie Sheen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 14, "question": "Matt Damon, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 15, "answer": "Terrific.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Matt Damon"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "What would you make him do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "Well, this is a -- you know, my mother is a professor of early childhood education.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "Who the hell are you guys?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "We are the people who make sure things happen according to plan.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "Now that is the moment in the movie when you kind of realized life is not going to be quite the same again, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "WP", ":", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "Has she gotten more dangerous as the last two years have progressed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "No, what -- what I actually said was, I thought of a really reasonable thing at the time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 95, "question": "What do you think of her now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 96, "answer": "Well, I mean, I disagree with her politically.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "You didn't watch \"Sarah Palin in Alaska\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "I didn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sarah Palin"], "LOCATION": ["Alaska"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "Are you a fan?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "No?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 131, "question": "Did you start a small business with your tax break?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": "I did not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "Again, does that come back to your sort of slightly disillusioned view of Obama, that when you voted for audacity of hope it wouldn't have been giving the rich tax breaks and watching 10 percent of your population remain unemployed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "RB", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "CD", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["10 percent"], "LOCATION": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "Have we still got hope, you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "Oh, man.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "When I hear you speak like this, I mean, the obvious question to ask you is, do you have political aspiration at all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "Not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "And if not, why don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "RB", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "Well, I'm really interested in politics.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "What's the single most effective thing you could do with that if you had your adjustment bureau hat on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "Well, the thing is with water there's not like -- there's not a magic bullet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", ":", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 219, "question": "If you had the power to have some kind of control over your four daughters, would you take it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "CD", "NNS", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 220, "answer": "There's no adjustment bureau in the world that -- yes, you know, it is very challenging and very fun to have four girls.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 231, "question": "I mean if you were advising a young guy who had a big hit movie, what did George say to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "NNP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 232, "answer": "Well, the first thing he said the first day I met him was don't let them keep you inside.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "RB", ":", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "By that you mean physically in your home?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "Physically don't -- just because they're -- the celebrity can feel a little oppressive.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "Do you think, wow, this is what I've lived for, this moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "Well, the work part, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "RBS", "VBG", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "RBS", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "And why did you think that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "Because I've got the most amazing family, and I've got the most amazing wife.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "Has there been a moment when you could have veered down the Charlie Sheen route?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "Sure, there's always a moment for anybody.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie Sheen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "TO", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "Would you encourage a daughter of yours to be an actress?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "No, and my parents didn't encourage me to -- well, they didn't discourage me from being an actor.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 287, "question": "I mean, when I say superstar, how do you react to that phrase?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "It just seems funny to me to talk about --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "Is it ludicrous?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "To me, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 293, "question": "Because you're really -- you're Matt Damon, you're a human being, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "VBG", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 294, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Matt Damon"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "TO", "DT", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 297, "question": "How do you stay normal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 298, "answer": "The best answer I ever heard to that was George.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Hollywood"]}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "What's the secret to a successful marriage in Hollywood?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "Well, we don't live in Hollywood.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Hollywood"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "Are you easy to live with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "I'm sure I'm not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "You got a two-week rule?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "You aren't allowed to be apart for more than two weeks?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "JJR", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "NNP", "IN", "``", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 333, "question": "Like George in \"Up in the Air\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "IN", "``", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "I was basically George in \"Up in the Air.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "I have?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "You have.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 350, "question": "Yes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 351, "answer": "I think he's a terrific actor.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNS"], "qSentId": 357, "question": "That's pretty high praise, wasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "I was -- this is funny because my wife and I -- this is going to sound like I'm blowing smoke but we were sitting in bed watching PIERS", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 394, "question": "Will there be a fourth \"Bourne\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "``", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "I really hope so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Paul"]}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "With Paul Greengrass?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "With Paul.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Paul Greengrass"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "Do you believe that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben"]}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "NN", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "WP", "NNP", "VBD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "Do you ever think, what would I have done?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "Well, we just would have written another movie and gone and done it, which is what Ben did do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 429, "question": "Who would be the leading man, leading lady, producer, director?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "VBG", "NN", ",", "VBG", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "Well, my hope is to start directing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris Moore", "Chris", "John Gordon"]}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "Who's the producer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "Well, Chris Moore, who produced \"Good Will Hunting,\" my old friend, Chris and John Gordon, those guys.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "Leading man, leading lady?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NN", ",", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "Oh, I mean, it always depends on the job.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "Ben's the leading man?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "Ben would be my leading man.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Emily Blunt"]}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "Leading lady?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "I wouldn't do too bad with Emily Blunt.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "What would Emily say, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "I have no idea, but I'm dying to find out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "Should we find out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "I would love to find out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "What's happening to me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "We're being chased.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 488, "question": "What would you do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "Might infuse some women into \"The Adjustment Bureau.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "-- flying the sisterhood flag now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "JJR", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 501, "question": "What would it be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "I agree with you that it's hard not to sound pageantesque when you answer this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 522, "question": "Isn't that it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 523, "answer": "Well, I said, that is exactly it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "If you had that power?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "I left home at a very young age.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "If you hadn't made the sacrifices, would you be sitting here now as the star of a big movie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "I wouldn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "WP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "What would be the moment, Matt?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "Boy, I -- I kind of wonder what the next moment is.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Matt?"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Emily Blunt"]}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "What about professionally for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "Working with Emily Blunt.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "JJ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "What would be the moment you'd relive?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "You know, I -- I would relive -- right now -- I would relive all four years of college in ten minutes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 608, "question": "Is it because you don't have any responsibilities?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 609, "answer": "You have nothing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "What about you, John?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "Oh, I'm going to bring it down now.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John?"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 640, "question": "So what are the faults of Mr. Perfect?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 641, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Perfect"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 672, "question": "Did you do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 673, "answer": "Yes, he did do that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Judi Dench"]}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 685, "question": "How important is humor on the sets of these things?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 686, "answer": "I did my first job with Judi Dench.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 712, "question": "Are you in it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 713, "answer": "No, I'm kidding.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jesse Owens"]}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 723, "question": "Jesse Owens I'm hearing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 724, "answer": "Jesse Owens, working on it, trying to get it made.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jesse Owens"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 731, "question": "What happened to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 732, "answer": "I got old, man.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lupo"]}, "docId": "110303pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBN", "``", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 743, "question": "What are you up to next?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 744, "answer": "I'm about to start a film in march called \"Lupo.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]